A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20 FA292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Files, 1920-1993; 2; 242 Box(es)
  - Blacklocks, Stephen Roy - 1981 - England - Philosophy, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - Blackman, David John - 1968 - England - Greek History and Archaeology, 1967-1983 (Box 18, Folder 151)
  - Blair, William Sutherland - 1940 - Scotland - Economics, 1940-1975 (Box 18, Folder 152)
  - Blake, John Lucian - 1937 - England - Law, 1937-1949 (Box 18, Folder 153)
  - Blakeley, Roger William George - 1980 - New Zealand - Engineering, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 154)
  - Blakemore, Collin Brian - 1965 - England - Physiology, 1964-1989 (Box 18, Folder 155)
  - Blankert, Albert - 1968 - Netherlands - Art History, 1968-1980 (Box 19, Folder 156)
  - Blaxter, Kenneth Lyon - 1946 - Scotland - Agriculture, 1946-1985 (Box 19, Folder 157)
  - Bloch, Daniel - 1960 - France - Mass Media, 1959-1974 (Box 19, Folder 158)
  - Bloxam, Thomas Wallace - 1954 - England - Petrology, 1953-1984 (Box 19, Folder 159)
  - Bloxham, Michael John William - 1967 - England - Physics, 1967-1982 (Box 19, Folder 160)
  - Blundell, Peter Charles - 1936 - England - History, 1937-1943 (Box 19, Folder 161)
  - Boden, Margaret Ann - 1962 - England - Psychology, 1961-1988 (Box 19, Folder 162)
  - Boettcher, Barry - 1968 - Australia - Genetics, 1968-1975 (Box 20, Folder 163)
  - Bollard, Edward George - 1956 - New Zealand - Plant Physiology, 1955-1985 (Box 20, Folder 164)
  - Bolognesi, Martino - 1976 - Italy - Biological Chemistry, 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 165)
  - Bonarius, Joannes Cornelius Josephus - 1962 - Netherlands - Psychology, 1961-1975 (Box 20, Folder 166)
  - Bondy, Rupert Mark Boden - 1984 - London - Philosophy of Law, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 167)
  - Bone, James - 1983 - England - International Relations, 1982-1990 (Box 20, Folder 168)
  - Bongard, Karl Wilhelm - 1965 - Germany - Art, 1964-1983 (Box 20, Folder 169)
  - Bonham Carter, Mark Raymond - 1947 - England - Political Theory, 1947-1989 (Box 20, Folder 170)
  - Bookbinder, Alan Peter - 1978 - England - Soviet Studies, 1977-1990 (Box 20, Folder 171)
  - Booth, Clive - 1973 - England - Educational Finance, 1972-1988 (Box 21, Folder 172)
  - Boshier, John - 1976 - New Zealand - Energy Systems, 1975-1982 (Box 21, Folder 173)
  - Bostock, Peter Alan - 1972 - England - Business Administration, 1971-1979 (Box 21, Folder 174)
  - Bottelier, Peter Paulus Carolus - 1962 - Netherlands - Economics, 1961-1986 (Box 21, Folder 175)
  - Bottral, Francis James Ronald - 1931 - England - English Literature, 1931-1986 (Box 21, Folder 176)
  - Boulding, Kenneth Ewart - 1932 - England - Economics, 1932-1986 (Box 21, Folder 177)
  - Bowen, Gordon - 1936 - England - Economic Georgraphy, 1936-1975 (Box 22, Folder 178)
  - Box, Pelham Horton - 1925 - England - History, 1925-1927 (Box 22, Folder 179)
  - Boyle, James Anthony - 1968 - Scotland - Biochemistry, 1967-1988 (Box 22, Folder 180)
  - Bradburn, Mary - 1950 - England - Mathematical Physics, 1949-1980 (Box 22, Folder 181)
  - Bradbury, Ronald - 1931 - England - Architecture, 1931-1973 (Box 22, Folder 182)
  - Bradfield, John Richard Grenfall - 1948 - England - Cytochecmistry, 1948-1990 (Box 22, Folder 183)
  - Bradley, John Newton - 1957 - England - Chemistry, 1956-1985 (Box 22, Folder 184)
  - Bradshaw, Eric Jean - 1929 - Ireland - Engineering, 1929-1974 (Box 22, Folder 185)
  - Bragg, Stephen Lawrence - 1948 - England - Mechanical Engineering, 1948-1988 (Box 23, Folder 186)
  - Brambilla, Roberto - 1968 - Italy - Architecture, 1967-1976 (Box 23, Folder 187)
  - Brambilla, Roberto - 1968 - Italy - Architecture, 1967-1976 (Box 23, Folder 188)
  - Brandenburger, Adam Maurice - 1983 - England - Economics, 1982-1987 (Box 23, Folder 189)
  - Brands, Maarten Cornelis - 1966 - Netherlands - History, 1966-1986 (Box 23, Folder 190)
  - Branson, David - 1965 - England - Physics, 1965-1975 (Box 23, Folder 191)
  - Bray, Williams John - 1955 - England - Telecommunications, 1955-1988 (Box 23, Folder 192)
  - Breal, Jean-Pierre - 1967 - France - Economics, 1966-1980 (Box 23, Folder 193)
  - Bressand, Albert - 1975 - France - Political Economics, 1975-1978 (Box 24, Folder 194)
  - Brett, George - 1927 - England - Physics, 1927-1990 (Box 24, Folder 195)
  - Brewer, Frederick - 1925 - England - Chemistry, 1925-1963 (Box 24, Folder 196)
  - Brill, Patrick James - 1988 - England - Painting, 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 197)
  - Brinker, Helmut - 1966 - Germany - Art History, 1965-1985 (Box 24, Folder 198)
  - Brittain, Robert Peter - 1947 - Scotland - Legal Medicine, 1947-1972 (Box 24, Folder 199)
  - Broadbent, Richard John - 1983 - England - Industrial Relations, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 200)
  - Broadhurst, David John - 1971 - England - Physics, 1970-1975 (Box 24, Folder 201)
  - Brock, William Ranulf - 1954 - Scotland - American History, 1952-1980 (Box 24, Folder 202)
  - Brodie, Jean Pamela - 1980 - England - Astronomy, 1980-1986 (Box 25, Folder 203)
  - Broerson, Theodorus - 1973 - Netherlands - Political Science, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 204)
  - Brogan, Denis Hugh - 1962 - England - History, 1961-1988 (Box 25, Folder 205)
  - Brooke, Peter Leonard - 1957 - England - Business Administration, 1956-1989 (Box 25, Folder 206)
  - Brown, Archibald - 1948 - Australia - Astronomy, 1948-1990 (Box 25, Folder 207)
  - Brown, Arthur - 1953 - England - Literature, 1952-1980 (Box 25, Folder 208)
  - Brown, George Malcolm - 1954 - England - Geology, 1952-1990 (Box 25, Folder 209)
  - Brown, John - 1934 - England - Philosophy, 1934-1980 (Box 25, Folder 210)
  - Brown, Leslie Christine - 1978 - England - Chemistry, 1977-1990 (Box 25, Folder 211)
  - Browne, Philip Austin - 1937 - England - Music, 1937-1961 (Box 26, Folder 212)
  - Browse, Norman - 1964 - England - Vascular Physiology, 1963-1985 (Box 26, Folder 213)
  - Brumley, John Charles - 1974 - Australia - Geology, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 214)
  - Brumm, Ursula Maria - 1953 - Germany - American Studies, 1953-1975 (Box 26, Folder 215)
  - Brunskill, Ronald William - 1956 - England - Architecture, 1955-1990 (Box 26, Folder 216)
  - Brusse, Mark - 1965 - Netherlands - Sculpture, 1964-1967 (Box 26, Folder 217)
  - Bryce, Robert - 1935 - Canada - Economics, 1935-1980 (Box 26, Folder 218)
  - Bryer, Monte Leo - 1937 - England - Architecture, 1937-1986 (Box 26, Folder 219)
  - Bryson, David Carruthers - 1938 - England - Political Science, 1938-1979 (Box 26, Folder 220)
  - Bryson, William Norman - 1970 - England - Literature, 1969-1989 (Box 26, Folder 221)
  - Buisson, David - 1983 - New Zealand - Horticulture, 1982-1986 (Box 27, Folder 222)
  - Bunker, Nicholas Philip - 1981 - England - Literature, 1980-1985 (Box 27, Folder 223)
  - Bunton, Clifford - 1948 - England - Chemistry, 1948-1975 (Box 27, Folder 224)
  - Burchi, Stefano - 1976 - Italy - Law, 1975-1986 (Box 27, Folder 225)
  - Burnet, James William Alexander - 1956 - England - Journalism, 1956-1990 (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - Burns, Malcolm McRae - 1934 - New Zealand - Science, 1934-1987 (Box 27, Folder 227)
  - Burns, Sandra Pauline - 1961 - England - Law, 1961-1989 (Box 27, Folder 228)
  - Burnside, Madeleine Hilding - 1970 - England - Art History, 1970-1975 (Box 27, Folder 229)
  - Burnside, William Hunniford Lauder - 1975 - England - Business Administration, 1974-1985 (Box 27, Folder 230)
  - Burrows, Andrew - 1980 - England - Law, 1979-1987 (Box 28, Folder 231)
  - Burstall, Timothy - 1965 - Australia - Film, 1964-1985 (Box 28, Folder 232)
  - Bush, Ian Elcock - 1952 - England - Biochemistry, 1951-1986 (Box 28, Folder 233)
  - Butcher, Alfred Dunabavin - 1954 - England - Fisheries Management, 1953-1975 (Box 28, Folder 234)
  - Butchers, Judith - 1979 - Australia - Law, 1978-1985 (Box 28, Folder 235)
  - Butler, Percy - 1936 - England - Zoology, 1936-1984 (Box 28, Folder 236)
  - Butler, Alan Clive - 1968 - England - Business Administration, 1967-1990 (Box 28, Folder 237)
  - Butlin, Matthew - 1977 - Australia - Economics, 1976-1987 (Box 28, Folder 238)
  - Byatt, Ian Charles Rayner - 1957 - England - Economics, 1956-1989 (Box 28, Folder 239)
  - Byng, Sally Catherine - 1989 - England - Speech Therapy, 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 240)
  - Calasso, Gian Petro - 1964 - Italy - Drama, 1962-1981 (Box 29, Folder 241)
  - Calne, Roy York - 1960 - England - Medical Science, 1959-1990 (Box 29, Folder 242)
  - Calogero, Francesco - 1961 - Italy - Physics, 1959-1975 (Box 29, Folder 243)
  - Calthrop, Michael John - 1962 - England - Architecture, 1961-1980 (Box 29, Folder 244)
  - Calthrop, Paul Wyndham Clayton - 1977 - England - Business Administration, 1976-1982 (Box 29, Folder 245)
  - Calveley, Charles Edward - 1947 - England - Business Administration, 1947-1988 (Box 29, Folder 246)
  - Calvert, John - 1930 - England - Engineering, 1930-1972 (Box 29, Folder 247)
  - Calza, Gian Carlo - 1966 - Italy - Oriental Studies, 1965-1984 (Box 29, Folder 248)
  - Calzini, Paolo Giorgio - 1958 - Italy - International Affairs, 1957-1986 (Box 30, Folder 249)
  - Cameron, John Robinson - 1959 - Scotland - Mathematics, 1958-1984 (Box 30, Folder 250)
  - Cameron, Robert Laurence - 1979 - New Zealand - Public Administration, 1978-1985 (Box 30, Folder 251)
  - Cameron, William James Gardiner - 1947 - Ireland - Mathematics, 1947-1979 (Box 30, Folder 252)
  - Cammarata, Cataldo - 1977 - France - Law, 1976-1985 (Box 30, Folder 253)
  - Campbell, Alastair Vincent - 1962 - England - Theology, 1962-1988 (Box 30, Folder 254)
  - Campbell, Andrew - 1976 - England - Business Administration, 1976-1988 (Box 30, Folder 255)
  - Campbell, Isabel Grace - 1930 - England - Organic Chemistry, 1930-1990 (Box 30, Folder 256)
  - Campbell, Richard - 1929 - New Zealand - Economics, 1929-1958 (Box 31, Folder 257)
  - Campbell, William - 1925 - Scotland - Chemistry, 1925-1982 (Box 31, Folder 258)
  - Campling, Anthony - 1967 - England - Business Administration, 1966-1985 (Box 31, Folder 259)
  - Candel, Sebastien Mathieu - 1968 - France - Mathematical Engineering, 1967-1973 (Box 31, Folder 260)
  - Candlin, David John - 1955 - England - Physics, 1954-1985 (Box 31, Folder 261)
  - Cannings, Della Maria - 1982 - England - Sociology, 1981-1990 (Box 31, Folder 262)
  - Cannings, Della Maria - 1982 - England - Sociology, 1981-1990 (Box 31, Folder 263)
  - Cannan, Bernard - 1938 - England - Mathematics, 1938-1986 (Box 31, Folder 264)
  - Cannings, Hugh - 1964 - England - Architecture, 1963-1982 (Box 31, Folder 265)
  - Not Used (Box 31, Folder 266)
  - Carbonel, Sylvie - 1972 - France - Music, 1971-1985 (Box 32, Folder 267)
  - Carbonel, Sylvie - 1972 - France - Music, 1971-1985 (Box 32, Folder 268)
  - Carbonel, Sylvie - 1972 - France - Music, 1971-1985 (Box 32, Folder 269)
  - Carboni, Guido - 1972 - Italy - American Literature, 1969-1989 (Box 32, Folder 270)
  - Carey, Frances Anne - 1970 - England - Art history, 1969-1985 (Box 32, Folder 271)
  - Cargill, Thompson William David - 1957 - England - History, 1956-1978 (Box 32, Folder 272)
  - Carmichael, John - 1933 - England - Mathematics, 1933-1988 (Box 32, Folder 273)
  - Carroll, John Laurance - 1963 - Australia - Mathematics and Statistics, 1963-1975 (Box 32, Folder 274)
  - Carstairs, Andrew Damarell - 1969 - England - Linguistics, 1968-1981 (Box 33, Folder 275)
  - Carstairs, George - 1948 - England - Anthropology, 1948-1990 (Box 33, Folder 276)
  - Cartledge, Bryan George - 1956 - England - Russian History, 1955-1988 (Box 33, Folder 277)
  - Cary, Anthony Joyce - 1980 - England - Business Administration, 1979-1990 (Box 33, Folder 278)
  - Cassen, Robert Harvey - 1959 - England - Economics, 1957-1987 (Box 33, Folder 279)
  - Cassidy, John Joseph - 1984 - England - History, 1983-1990 (Box 33, Folder 280)
  - Cassidy, Michael - 1968 - England - Architecture and Urban Planning, 1967-1988 (Box 33, Folder 281)
  - Catto, Graeme - 1975 - England - Medical and Biomedical Science, 1974-1989 (Box 33, Folder 282)
  - Caulcott, Thomas Holt - 1960 - England - Political Science, Public Control and International Relations, 1959-1988 (Box 34, Folder 283)
  - Caunce, Fred - 1955 - England - Chemical Engineering, 1955-1986 (Box 34, Folder 284)
  - Cavalli, Alessandro - 1965 - Italy - Sociology, 1963-1985 (Box 34, Folder 285)
  - Cavander, Kenneth - 1963 - England - American Theatre, 1962-1985 (Box 34, Folder 286)
  - Cawte, John Ewart - 1955 - Australia - Social Psychiatry, 1955-1984 (Box 34, Folder 287)
  - Ceccarelli, Paulo - 1963 - Italy - Architecture, 1962-1980 (Box 34, Folder 288)
  - Cecil, Hugh - 1967 - England - History, 1967-1984 (Box 34, Folder 289)
  - Chain, Benjamin - 1980 - England - Immunology, 1980-1983 (Box 34, Folder 290)
  - Chaloner, William Gilbert - 1953 - England - Paleobotany, 1953-1990 (Box 35, Folder 291)
  - Chambers, Frank Pentland - 1926 - England - Architecture, 1926-1964 (Box 35, Folder 292)
  - Champeaux, Alain - 1972 - France - Economics, 1971-1985 (Box 35, Folder 293)
  - Chandler, Geoffrey - 1953 - England - Economic Policy, 1952-1987 (Box 35, Folder 294)
  - Chantler, Philip - 1934 - England - Economics, 1934-1987 (Box 35, Folder 295)
  - Chapman, Timothy Frank - 1983 - England - Anthropology, 1982-1988 (Box 35, Folder 296)
  - Chaput, Hughes Michel - 1971 - France - Operational Research, 1970-1987 (Box 35, Folder 297)
  - Charles, Bruce - 1975 - Australia - Pharmaceutical Science, 1974-1990 (Box 36, Folder 298)
  - Chenut, Daniel - 1962 - France - Architecture, 1961-1981 (Box 36, Folder 299)
  - Chester Jones, Ian - 1947 - England - Endocrinology, 1947-1984 (Box 36, Folder 300)
  - Chester Jones, Ian - 1947 - England - Endocrinology, 1947-1984 (Box 36, Folder 301)
  - Chester, Lewis Alexander - 1967 - England - Politics, 1965-1990 (Box 36, Folder 302)
  - Chesters, John Hugh - 1932 - England - Ceramics, 1932-1990 (Box 36, Folder 303)
  - Child, Clifton James - 1936 - England - American History, 1936-1988 (Box 37, Folder 304)
  - Chipperfield, Geoffrey Howes - 1962 - England - Government Administration, 1961-1988 (Box 37, Folder 305)
  - Chrimes, Neil Roy - 1977 - England - Economics, 1976-1990 (Box 37, Folder 306)
  - Christelow, Allan - 1934 - England - History, 1934-1980 (Box 37, Folder 307)
  - Churches, Malcolm - 1969 - New Zealand - Police Administration, 1969-1986 (Box 37, Folder 308)
  - Cillie, Gabriel Gideon - 1933 - England - Astronomy, 1933-1986 (Box 37, Folder 309)
  - Clancy, Laurence - 1966 - Australia - American Literature, 1966-1975 (Box 37, Folder 310)
  - Clark, Christopher Frederick - 1974 - England - History, 1973-1990 (Box 38, Folder 311)
  - Clark, Jennifer - 1982 - Australia - History, 1981-1987 (Box 38, Folder 312)
  - Clark, John Richard James - 1965 - Australia - Drama, 1964-1981 (Box 38, Folder 313)
  - Clark, William Donaldson - 1938 - England - Philosophy, 1938-1985 (Box 38, Folder 314)
  - Clarke, John Colin - 1957 - England - Nuclear Engineering, 1956-1989 (Box 38, Folder 315)
  - Cleaver, Richard Edward Lionel - 1948 - England - Industrial Studies, 1948-1986 (Box 38, Folder 316)
  - Cleaver, Richard Edward Lionel - 1948 - England - Industrial Studies, 1948-1986 (Box 38, Folder 317)
  - Clifford, Tom Neville - 1954 - England - Geology, 1954-1975 (Box 38, Folder 318)
  - Clyne, Henry Horne - 1959 - Scotland - Sculpture, 1958-1990 (Box 39, Folder 319)
  - Coaldrake, John Edward - 1957 - Australia - Ecology, 1957-1987 (Box 39, Folder 320)
  - Cobb, Frederick Peter - 1952 - England - Community Development, 1952-1982 (Box 39, Folder 321)
  - Cohen, Andrew Benjamin - 1938 - England - History, 1929-1965 (Box 39, Folder 322)
  - Cohen, Harold - 1959 - England - Painting, 1959-1982 (Box 39, Folder 323)
  - Cohen, Laurence Jonathan - 1952 - England - Logic, 1951-1989 (Box 39, Folder 324)
  - Cohen, Rosalyn - 1959 - England - International Law, 1958-1990 (Box 39, Folder 325)
  - Cohen, Ruth Louisa - 1930 - England - Agricultural Economics, 1930-1987 (Box 39, Folder 326)
  - Cohen, Wilby, Edison - 1935 - Australia - Industrial Research, 1934-1966 (Box 40, Folder 327)
  - Cohors-Fresentborg, Monika - 1976 - Germany - Psychology, 1975-1986 (Box 40, Folder 328)
  - Colbourne, John - 1963 - England - Engineering, 1961-1986 (Box 40, Folder 329)
  - Coles, John - 1934 - South Africa - Pathology, 1933-1987 (Box 40, Folder 330)
  - Collart, Yves Marcel - 1955 - Switzerland - Social History, 1954-1980 (Box 40, Folder 331)
  - Collee, George Galbraith - 1984 - England - Medicine, 1984-1987 (Box 40, Folder 332)
  - Collings, Thomas - 1963 - England - Theology, 1963-1987 (Box 40, Folder 333)
  - Collins, Bruce William - 1972 - England - American Studies, 1971-1989 (Box 40, Folder 334)
  - Collins, John David - 1982 - Australia - Philosophy, 1981-1986 (Box 40, Folder 335)
  - Collop, David John - 1971 - England - Physics, 1970-1980 (Box 41, Folder 336)
  - Colman, Anna Frances - 1988 - England - Violin Studies, 1987-1990 (Box 41, Folder 337)
  - Colman, John Stacy - 1931 - England - Biology, 1931-1981 (Box 41, Folder 338)
  - Colombo, Paolo - 1975 - Italy - American Literature, 1974-1986 (Box 41, Folder 339)
  - Connolly, Justin - 1963 - England - Music, 1962-1990 (Box 41, Folder 340)
  - Connor, Kevin Leslie - 1966 - Australia - Painting, 1965-1985 (Box 41, Folder 341)
  - Conway, Alan - 1954 - England - American History, 1953-1975 (Box 41, Folder 342)
  - Conyngham, Barry Ernest - 1972 - Australia - Music, 1971-1985 (Box 41, Folder 343)
  - Cook, Helena Mary - 1983 - England - Law, 1982-1987 (Box 42, Folder 344)
  - Cooke, Alfred Alistair - 1932 - England - Literature, 1932-1989 (Box 42, Folder 345)
  - Cooke, Arthur Francis Benn - 1928 - England - Law, 1928-1986 (Box 42, Folder 346)
  - Coombs, Herbert Isaac - 1927 - England - Medicine, 1927-1973 (Box 42, Folder 347)
  - Cooper, Aldwyn John Richard - 1973 - England - Psychology, 1973-1980 (Box 42, Folder 348)
  - Corben, Herbert Charles - 1939 - England - Physics, 1939-1981 (Box 42, Folder 349)
  - Coren, Alan - 1961 - England - American Literature, 1961-1989 (Box 42, Folder 350)
  - Cornford, James Peters - 1960 - England - Political Sociology, 1960-1989 (Box 43, Folder 351)
  - Corpet, Francois - 1961 - France - Business Administration, 1959-1975 (Box 43, Folder 352)
  - Costa, Giacomo Girolamo - 1967 - Italy - Economics, 1966-1980 (Box 43, Folder 353)
  - Coudol, Jaques - 1965 - France - Business and Industrial Studies, 1963-1980 (Box 43, Folder 354)
  - Cowan, Andrew Gillespie - 1938 - Canada - Economics, 1938-1985 (Box 43, Folder 355)
  - Cowan, William Dean Trafford - 1970 - Australia - Business Administration, 1970-1985 (Box 43, Folder 356)
  - Cowley, Steven Charles - 1981 - England - Physics, 1980-1985 (Box 43, Folder 357)
  - Cox, Barry - 1959 - England - Biological Science, 1958-1988 (Box 43, Folder 358)
  - Craik, James - 1925 - Scotland - Chemistry, 1925-1975 (Box 44, Folder 359)
  - Crane, Alexander Herbert - 1929 - Australia - Forestry, 1928-1975 (Box 44, Folder 360)
  - Cranswick, Margaret - 1926 - England - Education, 1926-1987 (Box 44, Folder 361)
  - Craske, Peter - 1965 - England - History, 1965-1986 (Box 44, Folder 362)
  - Craven, Charles Alexander Urton - 1939 - England - Geology, 1939-1984 (Box 44, Folder 363)
  - Crawford, John Grenfell - 1938 - England - Economics, 1937-1985 (Box 44, Folder 364)
  - Crease, Susan - 1976 - England - Electrical Engineering, 1975-1987 (Box 44, Folder 365)
  - Crichton, Richard Brian - 1967 - Australia - Painting, 1965-1972 (Box 45, Folder 366)
  - Crinion, David Ellis - 1954 - England - Architecture, 1953-1984 (Box 45, Folder 367)
  - Crocker, Walter Russell - 1928 - Australia - Demography, 1927-1984 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Croft, Nigel Howard - 1981 - England - Metallurgy, 1980-1990 (Box 45, Folder 369)
  - Crosbie, Sharon Margaret - 1984 - New Zealand - Journalism, 1983-1986 (Box 45, Folder 370)
  - Crosta, Pierluigi - 1966 - Italy - Architecture, 1965-1971 (Box 45, Folder 371)
  - Crowe, Percy Robert - 1928 - England - Geography, 1928-1980 (Box 45, Folder 372)
  - Crowther, Geoffrey - 1929 - England - Economics, 1929-1972 (Box 45, Folder 373)
  - Crowther-Hunt, Norman - 1951 - England - Political Science, 1950-1987 (Box 45, Folder 374)
  - Cruickshank, Alan - 1946 - England - Pathology, 1946-1975 (Box 46, Folder 375)
  - Cull, Nicholas John - 1988 - England - History, 1987-1990 (Box 46, Folder 376)
  - Cullen, John Carruthers - 1967 - Australia - Architecture, 1961-1985 (Box 46, Folder 377)
  - Cullen, John Carruthers - 1967 - Australia - Architecture, 1961-1985 (Box 46, Folder 378)
  - Culpin, Robert - 1976 - England - Public Administration, 1975-1984 (Box 46, Folder 379)
  - Cumming, George - 1928 - England - Geology, 1928-1954 (Box 46, Folder 380)
  - Cumpsty, John - 1956 - England - Industrial Administration, 1955-1976 (Box 46, Folder 381)
  - Cunliffe, Marcus - 1947 - England - History, 1947-1986 (Box 46, Folder 382)
  - Curnow, Robert Nicholas - 1959 - England - Statistics, 1958-1975 (Box 47, Folder 383)
  - Currall, Alexander - 1954 - England - Business and Industrial Studies, 1954-1988 (Box 47, Folder 384)
  - Curran, Alan Hamilton - 1972 - England - Physics, 1972-1985 (Box 47, Folder 385)
  - Curry, Robert Oswald Leonard - 1935 - England - Phonetics, 1935-1954 (Box 47, Folder 386)
  - Curtis, Anthony - 1958 - England - Literature and Drama, 1958-1985 (Box 47, Folder 387)
  - D'Aeth, Richard Hugh - 1936 - England - Biology, 1936-1990 (Box 47, Folder 388)
  - Dalgleish, Charles Edward - 1946 - England - Chemistry, 1946-1989 (Box 47, Folder 389)
  - Damazer, Mark David - 1977 - England - History, 1976-1990 (Box 47, Folder 390)
  - Danielli, James Frederic - 1933 - England - Biology, 1933-1988 (Box 47, Folder 391)
  - Dankwerts, Peter - 1946 - England - Engineering, 1946-1984 (Box 48, Folder 392)
  - Danskin, James Hunter - 1971 - England - Physics, 1970-1987 (Box 48, Folder 393)
  - Dark, Rex Sanders - 1968 - England - Mathematics, 1967-1978 (Box 48, Folder 394)
  - Darvall, Frank - 1929 - England - History, 1928-1987 (Box 48, Folder 395)
  - Darwin, Christopher - 1969 - England - Psychology, 1968-1988 (Box 48, Folder 396)
  - Dastgir, Rosemary Vanessa - 1989 - England - Film Studies, 1988-1991 (Box 48, Folder 397)
  - Davenport, Andrew Charles - 1977 - England - Political Science, 1975-1987 (Box 48, Folder 398)
  - Davidson, Jonathan Alastair - 1984 - England - Business Administration, 1983-1987 (Box 48, Folder 399)
  - Davies, Bernard - 1965 - England - Social Work, 1965-1988 (Box 49, Folder 400)
  - Davies, David James - 1927 - England - Law, 1927-1981 (Box 49, Folder 401)
  - Davies, Donald Watts - 1954 - England - Computer Technology, 1954-1988 (Box 49, Folder 402)
  - Davies, Handel - 1951 - England - Physics, 1950-1988 (Box 49, Folder 403)
  - Davies, Howard - 1979 - England - Management Studies, 1978-1990 (Box 49, Folder 404)
  - Davies, Jack Neville Phillips - 1949 - England - Pathology, 1948-1975 (Box 49, Folder 405)
  - Davies, Louis Walter - 1958 - Australia - Physics, 1958-1975 (Box 49, Folder 406)
  - Davies, Morgan Wynn Humphrey - 1938 - England - Engineering, 1938-1984 (Box 49, Folder 407)
  - Davies, Peter Max - 1962 - England - Music Composition, 1961-1990 (Box 49, Folder 408)
  - Davies, William Hopkin - 1938 - England - History, 1938-1987 (Box 50, Folder 409)
  - Davies, William Thomas Pennar - 1936 - Wales - Literature, 1936-1982 (Box 50, Folder 410)
  - Davison, Ian Frederic Hay - 1957 - England - Business Administration, 1956-1990 (Box 50, Folder 411)
  - Dawson, Paul Michael - 1977 - England - Genetics, 1976-1987 (Box 50, Folder 412)
  - Day, Peter Rodney - 1954 - England - Genetics, 1953-1988 (Box 50, Folder 413)
  - Dean, James Malcolm - 1966 - England - Politics, 1965-1985 (Box 50, Folder 414)
  - DeAngelis, Lucio - 1966 - Italy - Agricultural Economics, 1964-1979 (Box 50, Folder 415)